mergernetwork.com 2008-10-02

# Businesses for Sale | Business for Sale Listings | Buy - Sell - Find A Business! | MergerNetwork.com

Mergernetwork.com (the "Site") is owned by Brauns Online Media, Inc. ("MergerNetwork"). MergerNetwork values your privacy and is dedicated to protecting your personal information and providing you with:

**Notice**

  * What personally identifiable information we collect
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared

**Consent**

  * What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of that information

**Security**

  * Procedures we use to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of that information

**Access**

  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information we have collected from you

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

_Tracking Technology._ MergerNetwork logs IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the Site. We may track your movement within the Site, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. We only use this information in aggregate and do not link it to you personally unless you opt in as a subscriber. To gauge the effectiveness of our Site, we do collect some generic information about our visitors. Our web servers automatically recognize a visitor's domain name, the web page from which a visitor enters our Site, which pages a visitor visits on our Site, and how much time a visitor spends on each page. We may use anonymous tracking technologies to collect, store and sometimes track information for statistical purposes and to improve the products and services we provide. We aggregate this information and use it to evaluate and improve our Site. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources for instance to verify your address or update your information and to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to improve the content of the Site for you. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this Site. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Persistent cookies are used to differentiate registered users from non-registered users, to differentiate logged-in users from non-logged-in users, to customize the content of certain sections of the website, to enable us to track and target the interests of our users, and to enhance the experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site may be limited.

_Registration:_ If you subscribe to the Basic Edition of our services, we will collect your name and email address. If you then upgrade to the Professional Edition, we will collect your billing information.

_Surveys:_ We may from time to time provide a survey for our subscribers to fill out providing us with demographic information (such as income level and gender). We encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our Site but participation is entirely voluntary.

_Third Party Links:_ We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by our Site.

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

_Third Party Offers:_ We do not share personally identifiable information with other third parties and will not use your information to send you information about third party offers. We will only use your information to further the business conducted on this Site. 

_Listings:_ Information you provide as a listing will be come public and your personal information will be posted along with a listing unless you choose to post a listing anonymously in which case we will forward contacts to your mailbox on the Site. When posting a listing, users are given the option of releasing their contact information to other users who have searches that match their criteria. This contact information is then shared with the users who have business listings that match their search criteria. Any information you post is public information and we cannot control what uses third parties may make of personal information you share in such a public forum. In addition, users searching the Site can view contact information (name, email and phone number) when they view a listing profile. Users can save their search criteria to have information about properties that match the specified criteria placed in their mailbox or emailed to them. Search critera and activity remains private to the individual user.

_Search Agents:_ If you create a search agent to automatically search for listings matching your criteria, we may use your email address to send you search agent notifications. If you do not wish to receive these notifications, you can make your preference known. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section of this Policy.

_Recommended Listings:_ If you choose to have us notify you about recommended listings, we may use your email address to send you the listing notifications. If you do not wish to receive these notifications, you can make your preference known. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section of this Policy.

_Unread Mail:_ We provide an internal messaging system that enables our subscribers to communicate with each other and with our customer service representatives. If you elect to have us notify you about unread messages in your inbox, we may use your email address to send you these notifications. If you do not wish to receive these notifications, you can make your preference known. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section of this Policy.

_Other Uses._ We may use your personal information to contact you about the services on our Site in which you have expressed an interest, for example, if you have contacted customer service or made an inquiry.

_Service-related Announcements:_ We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or the delivery of a service or product is delayed we might send you an email, or if there is some service issue with something you might have ordered. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to cancel your subscription by completing the contact form at <http://www.mergernetwork.com/help/writetous>.

_Exceptional Circumstances:_ If Brauns Online Media, Inc., or any of its lines of businesses or affiliated companies, is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, the relevant databases of MergerNetwork could, in whole or in part, be sold as part of that transaction. Therefore, information about our users, including personal information, will be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Site, our Services or sale or pledge of our company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. Information about our users, including personal information, may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where Brauns Online Media, Inc., or an affiliate, is seeking financing, investment, support, or funding. In such transactions, personal information will be subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained. We also may have to release personally identifying information when it is necessary to comply with judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, orders, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of MergerNetwork or others.

## CHOICE AND OPT OUT

You may opt-out of use of your information as set forth above by completing the contact form at <http://www.mergernetwork.com/help/writetous>. We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.

## ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by MergerNetwork is not correct, or should you wish to have your email address removed from our mailing list or contact information changed, please send us a message using the form at <http://www.mergernetwork.com/help/writetous>. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Use, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Site.

## HOW MERGERNETWORK PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATION

We have security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information, which you have given us in order to prevent unauthorized access. Keep in mind however, that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to log off when finished using a shared computer.

Our Site may also contain links to other Web Sites. Keep in mind that MergerNetwork does not control and is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of these other web sites.

## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is set forth below. Please make special note of the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information or how we keep your purchases anonymous, you will know because the Effective Date of the Privacy Policy will change. If we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information but you may not be able to use our Site or Services in the future. By using our Site or Services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

## DISPUTES

If you choose to visit the Site your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.

## HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, send us a message using the contact form at <http://www.mergernetwork.com/help/writetous>.

©2008 Brauns Online Media, Inc.  
Effective Date: July 1, 2007
